usharbors.com 2019-10-07

# Privacy Policy | US Harbors

## USHarbors Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

» To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

» To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

» To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

» To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

» To send periodic emails

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We also use third party programmatic advertisements on usharbors.com, specifically the Google AdSense program, Ezoic and the Marine Ad Network. These advertisers may use technology such as cookies when they advertise on our site. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.

For more information on Google’s Adsense program visit this link: <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>

For more information on Ezoic visit this link: <https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/usharbors.com>

For more information on the Marine Ad Network visit this link: <https://marineadnetwork.net/privacy-policy/>

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.usharbors.com  
PO Box 566  
Rockland, Maine 04841  
United States  
[[email protected]](https://www.usharbors.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#7e171018113e0b0d161f0c1c110c0d501d1113)

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy .
